### MEGAN REED, Product Designer —www.meganreed.com —reed.megan.n@gmail.com

Designer of experiences & digital products. Advocate of the user. Into hospitality/travel tech at the intersection of high-tech & high-touch. Successfully builds products with startups, high-growth & multi-national companies and teams around the world. Hits the ground running across the full spectrum of UX/product design—has a holistic view of entire product flow and dabbles in code to bring wireframes and visual designs to life.

## Recent Experience

#### Product Designer Remote 2016-19

Collaborates to deliver end-to-end user experience and product design for high-impact projects focused on hospitality & travel tech; presenting design solutions to Director and reporting to Senior Designer/Program Lead.

Primary design deliverables include UX ideation & strategy, user research, wireframes & prototypes, brand identity, usability tests, visual UI designs.

## Founder & Marketing Designer Miami 2015-17

**EveryBell** was built to bring luxury hotel-style services to residences and rentals; achieving recognition as a 2015 and 2016 Best of Miami Business (Hospitality-Small Business).

Designed & developed website and mobile app as a platform for service execution and mobile bookings; leading user research, product idea generation, visual design, wireframing & prototyping.

Concept-to-production on new product line targeted at scaling short-term rental services with packaged amenity delivery.

Managed content creation, brand identity, marketing designs and campaigns using analytics to effectively measure and focus on high-impact activities.

## Senior Manager, Marketing & Product Singapore 2013-15

At **Stamford**, managed a local team of 10+ and collaborated with remote team of 6, including designers & engineers; achieving aggressive business growth of 600% year-over-year.

Directed complete product design cycle to launch new web portal that caused user engagement and retention to shoot up 165%.

Creative direction from concept-to-execution on all marketing and digital products while responsible for \$1M budget; including marketing plan & campaign strategy, high-profile event execution, digital & print advertising, partnership negotiations, video & editorial content creation, etc.

#### Product Marketing Manager Singapore & Germany 2011-13

HRS The Hotel Portal is a leading corporate travel tech company in Europe—startup in terms of culture, multi-national in terms of scope. Collaborated with product/sales/marketing teams to increase user onboarding success for B2B portal; driving bookings up by 40% with pipeline of \$2M per campaign.

Selected by Executive team to re-design presentation for key global corporate partners; maximizing bottom-line profitability and increasing regional engagement by 200%.

#### **Education & Skills**

**UX/UI Design & Front-End Development** Bloc.io 2016-17 **B.S. Business Administration, Marketing** CCU 2002-06

**Continuing Education** Specialized courses, workshops, events focused on design systems & process, UX writing, entrepreneurship, AI, voice interaction design

**Primary Tools** Sketch, Adobe XD, Figma, InVision, HTML, CSS, GitHub (open to and experienced in using others)

# **Highlighted Projects**

**Hotelify Web** UX design and front-end development of website, UX strategy for back-end management web app used to scale guest services & communication for independant hotels.

**UpStay Mobile** Led concept-to-production product design cycle for mobile on-demand bookings. Followed lean startup, highly-iterative process with user data and insights informing design decisions.

**SommMe Chatbot Interaction** UX strategy & design for concept prototype of wine pairing app. Also owned product brand identity, user research, UI design.

myStamford Digital Complete responsibility for successful launch of digital learning and communication portal in remote/agile environment. User research, UX strategy, user testing, design & dev direction.

## Past Experience

Marketing | Management 2006-11 Colorado & Hawaii

Began at **Intuit**, responsible for regional territory marketing and merchandising for small business solutions and tax deduction software products. Continued on to manage brand development and marketing efforts for **GNC** and **Vitamin World**.

Early career culminated in driving guest experience initiatives at Four Seasons Hotels & Resorts - awarded collaborative responsibility on a \$1M re-design project for new restaurant concept; creative direction, menu design, PR & event planning - recognized as #1 Fine Dining Restaurant in Hawaii.